<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.6.1" created="2024-08-28 22:41" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>My WordPress Website</title>
	<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706</link>
	<description></description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 22:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706</wp:base_blog_url>

		<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login><![CDATA[admin]]></wp:author_login><wp:author_email><![CDATA[admin@localhost.com]]></wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[admin]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>

				
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>

		<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Hello world!]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=1</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://127.0.0.1:9400/?p=1</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[hello-world]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>1</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[A WordPress Commenter]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email><![CDATA[wapuu@wordpress.example]]></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>https://wordpress.org/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt><![CDATA[2024-07-23 15:44:55]]></wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi, this is a comment.
To get started with moderating, editing, and deleting comments, please visit the Comments screen in the dashboard.
Commenter avatars come from <a href="https://en.gravatar.com/">Gravatar</a>.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved><![CDATA[1]]></wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
							</wp:comment>
					</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[A new idea]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=4&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=4</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=4</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>I asked him if he was not dissatisfied with having so small a share of wealth, and none of those distinctions in the state which are the objects of ambition. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>4</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:53:56]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:53:56]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:53:56]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[pitch]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[The start of something]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=7&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=7</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=7</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The nobleman swung his glasses a little faster and stared down into the fire. "You see, Mr. Holmes," said he, "my wife was twenty before her father became a rich man. During that time she ran free in a mining camp and wandered through woods or mountains, so that her education has come from Nature rather than from the schoolmaster.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>7</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:54:49]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:54:49]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:54:49]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[pitch]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[The Bennets of Longbourn]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=9&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=9</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=9</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Oh! certainly,” cried his faithful assistant, “no one can be really esteemed accomplished who does not greatly surpass what is usually met with. A woman must have a thorough knowledge of music, singing, drawing, dancing, and the modern languages, to deserve the word; and besides all this, she must possess a certain something in her air and manner of walking, the tone of her voice, her address and expressions, or the word will be but half-deserved.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“All this she must possess,” added Darcy, “and to all this she must yet add something more substantial, in the improvement of her mind by extensive reading.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I am no longer surprised at your knowing only six accomplished women. I rather wonder now at your knowing any.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Are you so severe upon your own sex as to doubt the possibility of all this?”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I never saw such a woman. I never saw such capacity, and taste, and application, and elegance, as you describe united.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Mrs. Hurst and Miss Bingley both cried out against the injustice of her implied doubt, and were both protesting that they knew many women who answered this description, when Mr. Hurst called them to order, with bitter complaints of their inattention to what was going forward. As all conversation was thereby at an end, Elizabeth soon afterwards left the room.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>9</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:59:02]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:59:08]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 19:59:08]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[assigned]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Transylvanian nobels]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=11&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=11</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=11</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>27 July.--No news from Jonathan. I am getting quite uneasy about him, though why I should I do not know; but I do wish that he would write, if it were only a single line. Lucy walks more than ever, and each night I am awakened by her moving about the room. Fortunately, the weather is so hot that she cannot get cold; but still the anxiety and the perpetually being wakened is beginning to tell on me, and I am getting nervous and wakeful myself. Thank God, Lucy's health keeps up. Mr. Holmwood has been suddenly called to Ring to see his father, who has been taken seriously ill. Lucy frets at the postponement of seeing him, but it does not touch her looks; she is a trifle stouter, and her cheeks are a lovely rose-pink. She has lost that anæmic look which she had. I pray it will all last.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>3 August.--Another week gone, and no news from Jonathan, not even to Mr. Hawkins, from whom I have heard. Oh, I do hope he is not ill. He surely would have written. I look at that last letter of his, but somehow it does not satisfy me. It does not read like him, and yet it is his writing. There is no mistake of that. Lucy has not walked much in her sleep the last week, but there is an odd concentration about her which I do not understand; even in her sleep she seems to be watching me. She tries the door, and finding it locked, goes about the room searching for the key.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>6 August.--Another three days, and no news. This suspense is getting dreadful. If I only knew where to write to or where to go to, I should feel easier; but no one has heard a word of Jonathan since that last letter. I must only pray to God for patience. Lucy is more excitable than ever, but is otherwise well. Last night was very threatening, and the fishermen say that we are in for a storm. I must try to watch it and learn the weather signs. To-day is a grey day, and the sun as I write is hidden in thick clouds, high over Kettleness. Everything is grey--except the green grass, which seems like emerald amongst it; grey earthy rock; grey clouds, tinged with the sunburst at the far edge, hang over the grey sea, into which the sand-points stretch like grey fingers. The sea is tumbling in over the shallows and the sandy flats with a roar, muffled in the sea-mists drifting inland. The horizon is lost in a grey mist. All is vastness; the clouds are piled up like giant rocks, and there is a "brool" over the sea that sounds like some presage of doom. Dark figures are on the beach here and there, sometimes half shrouded in the mist, and seem "men like trees walking." The fishing-boats are racing for home, and rise and dip in the ground swell as they sweep into the harbour, bending to the scuppers. Here comes old Mr. Swales. He is making straight for me, and I can see, by the way he lifts his hat, that he wants to talk....</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>I have been quite touched by the change in the poor old man. When he sat down beside me, he said in a very gentle way:--</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:00:39]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:00:39]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:00:39]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[in-progress]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[A literary biography]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=13&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=13</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=13</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Had I been as attentive not to displease him as I ought to have been, I know not but this vigil might have been fulfilled; but I unluckily entered upon the controversy concerning the right of Great-Britain to tax America, and attempted to argue in favour of our fellow-subjects on the other side of the Atlantick. I insisted that America might be very well governed, and made to yield sufficient revenue by the means of INFLUENCE, as exemplified in Ireland, while the people might be pleased with the imagination of their participating of the British constitution, by having a body of representatives, without whose consent money could not be exacted from them. Johnson could not bear my thus opposing his avowed opinion, which he had exerted himself with an extreme degree of heat to enforce; and the violent agitation into which he was thrown, while answering, or rather reprimanding me, alarmed me so, that I heartily repented of my having unthinkingly introduced the subject. I myself, however, grew warm, and the change was great, from the calm state of philosophical discussion in which we had a little before been pleasingly employed.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>We were fatigued by the contest, which was produced by my want of caution; and he was not then in the humour to slide into easy and cheerful talk. It therefore so happened, that we were after an hour or two very willing to separate and go to bed.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>On Wednesday, September 24, I went into Dr. Johnson's room before he got up, and finding that the storm of the preceding night was quite laid, I sat down upon his bed-side, and he talked with as much readiness and good-humour as ever. He recommended to me to plant a considerable part of a large moorish farm which I had purchased, and he made several calculations of the expence and profit: for he delighted in exercising his mind on the science of numbers. He pressed upon me the importance of planting at the first in a very sufficient manner, quoting the saying 'In bello non licet bis errare:' and adding, 'this is equally true in planting.'</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>I spoke with gratitude of Dr. Taylor's hospitality; and, as evidence that it was not on account of his good table alone that Johnson visited him often, I mentioned a little anecdote which had escaped my friend's recollection, and at hearing which repeated, he smiled. One evening, when I was sitting with him, Frank delivered this message: 'Sir, Dr. Taylor sends his compliments to you, and begs you will dine with him to-morrow. He has got a hare.'--'My compliments (said Johnson,) and I'll dine with him--hare or rabbit.'</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After breakfast I departed, and pursued my journey northwards. I took my post-chaise from the Green Man, a very good inn at Ashbourne, the mistress of which, a mighty civil gentlewoman, courtseying very low, presented me with an engraving of the sign of her house; to which she had subjoined, in her own hand-writing, an address in such singular simplicity of style, that I have preserved it pasted upon one of the boards of my original Journal at this time, and shall here insert it for the amusement of my readers:--</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>'M. KILLINGLEY's duty waits upon Mr. Boswell, is exceedingly obliged to him for this favour; whenever he comes this way, hopes for a continuance of the same. Would Mr. Boswell name the house to his extensive acquaintance, it would be a singular favour conferr'd on one who has it not in her power to make any other return but her most grateful thanks, and sincerest prayers for his happiness in time, and in a blessed eternity.--Tuesday morn.'</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>I cannot omit a curious circumstance which occurred at Edensor-inn, close by Chatsworth, to survey the magnificence of which I had gone a considerable way out of my road to Scotland. The inn was then kept by a very jolly landlord, whose name, I think, was Malton. He happened to mention that 'the celebrated Dr. Johnson had been in his house.' I inquired WHO this Dr. Johnson was, that I might hear mine host's notion of him. 'Sir, (said he,) Johnson, the great writer; ODDITY, as they call him. He's the greatest writer in England; he writes for the ministry; he has a correspondence abroad, and lets them know what's going on.'</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>13</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:02:10]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:02:10]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:02:10]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[draft]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[History of a Young Lady's Entrance into the World ]]></title>
		<link>https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.7008088962774706/?p=15&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=15</link>
		<pubDate></pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://playground.wordpress.net/scope:0.1393048133337713/?p=15</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Yet so strong is the desire you have implanted in me to act with uprightness and propriety, that, however the weakness of my heart may distress and afflict me, it will never, I humbly trust, render me wilfully culpable. The wish of doing well governs every other, as far as concerns my conduct,-for am I not your child?-the creature of your own forming!-Yet, Oh Sir, friend, parent, of my heart!-my feelings are all at war with my duties! and, while I most struggle to acquire self-approbation, my peace, my happiness, my hopes,-are lost!</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>'Tis you alone can compose a mind so cruelly agitated: you, I well know, can feel pity for the weakness to which you are a stranger; and, though you blame the affliction, soothe and comfort the afflicted.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>MR. VILLARS TO EVELINA. Berry Hill, Oct. 3rd.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>YOUR last communication, my dearest child, is indeed astonishing; that an acknowledged daughter and heiress of Sir John Belmont should be at Bristol, and still my Evelina bear the name of Anville, is to me inexplicable; yet the mystery of the Lady Howard prepared me to expect something extraordinary upon Sir John Belmont's return to England.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Whoever this young lady may be, it is certain she now takes a place to which you have a right indisputable. An after-marriage I never heard of; yet, supposing such a one to have happened, Miss Evelyn was certainly the first wife, and therefore her daughter must, at least, be entitled to the name of Belmont.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Either there are circumstances in this affair at present utterly incomprehensible, or else some strange and most atrocious fraud has been practiced; which of these two is the case it now behoves us to enquire.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>My reluctance to this step gives way to my conviction of its propriety, since the reputation of your dear and much-injured mother must now either be fully cleared from blemish, or receive its final and indelible wound.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The public appearance of a daughter of Sir John Belmont will revive the remembrance of Miss Evelyn's story in all who have heard it,-who the mother was, will be universally demanded,-and if any other Lady Belmont should be named, the birth of my Evelina will receive a stigma, against which, honour, truth, and innocence may appeal in vain!-a stigma, which will eternally blast the fair fame of her virtuous mother, and cast upon her blameless self the odium of a title, which not all her purity can rescue from established shame and dishonour!</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>No, my dear child, no; I will not quietly suffer the ashes of your mother to be treated with ignominy! her spotless character shall be justified to the world-her marriage shall be acknowledged, and her child shall bear the name to which she is lawfully entitled.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>It is true, that Mrs. Mirvan would conduct this affair with more delicacy than Mrs. Selwyn; yet, perhaps, to save time, is of all considerations the most important, since the longer this mystery is suffered to continue, the more difficult may be rendered its explanation. The sooner, therefore, you can set out for town, the less formidable will be your task.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Let not your timidity, my dear love, depress your spirits: I shall, indeed, tremble for you at a meeting so singular and so affecting, yet there can be no doubt of the success of your application: I enclose a your unhappy mother, written, and reserved purposely for this occasion: Mrs. Clinton too, who attended her in her last illness, must accompany you to town.-But, without any other certificate of your birth, that which you carry in your countenance, as it could not be affected by artifice, so it cannot admit of a doubt.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>And now, my Evelina, committed at length to the care of your real parent, receive the fervent prayers, wishes, and blessings, of him who so fondly adopted you!</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>15</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:03:40]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[0000-00-00 00:00:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:03:40]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2024-08-28 20:03:40]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[pending]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
										<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
						</item>
				</channel>
</rss>
	